<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HardCIDR Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.hardcidr.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on HardCIDR Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 12:57:45 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.hardcidr.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Magnesium Supplement Reference</title>
      <link>https://blog.hardcidr.com/supplements/magnesium/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 12:57:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.hardcidr.com/supplements/magnesium/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a big advocate of science-backed supplements to optimize mental and physical performance. These articles represent my own distilled research on effectiveness, risk, and other things to consider before supplementing. To see what supplements I am currently taking, definitely check out the &amp;ldquo;My Current Supplements&amp;rdquo; article at the top of this section. Most of the sources are dervived from Examine.com, which is a great resource, but my intent is to distill it down and add my own research + anecdotes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taurine Supplement Reference</title>
      <link>https://blog.hardcidr.com/supplements/taurine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 12:57:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.hardcidr.com/supplements/taurine/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a big advocate of science-backed supplements to optimize mental and physical performance. These articles represent my own distilled research on effectiveness, risk, and other things to consider before supplementing. To see what supplements I am currently taking, definitely check out the &amp;ldquo;My Current Supplements&amp;rdquo; article at the top of this section. Most of the sources are dervived from Examine.com, which is a great resource, but my intent is to distill it down and add my own research + anecdotes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crash Dieting</title>
      <link>https://blog.hardcidr.com/health/crashdiets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 12:57:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.hardcidr.com/health/crashdiets/</guid>
      <description>Crash diets, as a general rule of thumb, are a stupid idea. However, as laid out in my mid-December post On Fitness and Diet - Fighting \&amp;ldquo;Skinny Fat\&amp;rdquo;, the weight loss program I set out for myself was exactly that. I&amp;rsquo;m writing this followup post to outline my experience so far, and how I have come to embrace a properly controlled crash diet.
What I Did Crash dieting is all about restricting calories while juggling your micronutrient and macronutrient intake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crossing Your Tees: Bug Hunting for Fashion</title>
      <link>https://blog.hardcidr.com/security/crossingyourtees/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 12:57:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.hardcidr.com/security/crossingyourtees/</guid>
      <description>Note: Bonobos has been contacted about this issue and has been taken care of. All of the codes are dead now anyway :P
Every year for the past couple of years the online retailer Bonobos.com has held an &amp;ldquo;Easter Egg Hunt&amp;rdquo; on their website. This is typically a fun event whereby you check various pages on their website for codes used to unlock store credit, discounts, and other goodies. The main prize this year was a $500 voucher off any order, but you had to be the first to find and use the code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Losing Weight - Old</title>
      <link>https://blog.hardcidr.com/health/losingweight/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 12:57:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.hardcidr.com/health/losingweight/</guid>
      <description>The Myth of &amp;ldquo;Gaining Muscle While Losing Fat&amp;rdquo;        I usually blog about technology, trends, and industry news on a less-than-frequent basis, but I&amp;rsquo;m taking a sharp left turn with this blog post to talk about something personal - diet and fitness. I&amp;rsquo;ve spent the last two years trying to improve and iterate on my physical well-being to some degree of success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Analysis of the 2012 Election</title>
      <link>https://blog.hardcidr.com/sideprojects/2012electionsocialmedia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 12:57:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.hardcidr.com/sideprojects/2012electionsocialmedia/</guid>
      <description>The big question that comes up every four years always winds up being - how can we best quantify a presidential debate? CNN has tried quantifying public opinion around the debates with it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;undecided voter&amp;rdquo; sentiment, rudimentary Twitter analysis, and polling random joes on the street. The problem with these studies is one simple thing - sample size and error. In a world where 1%-2% more votes means victory or defeat, we cannot have small sample sizes that lead to 4-5% error.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trading Forex Based On Social Media Indicators</title>
      <link>https://blog.hardcidr.com/sideprojects/teamforex/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 12:57:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.hardcidr.com/sideprojects/teamforex/</guid>
      <description>The popular game show *Who Wants to Be a Millionaire* used to fascinate me as a child. The show itself was entertaining, novel for the time, and dramatic (“Is that your final answer?” anyone?). However, one part of the Millionaire always stuck out to me: why was the audience always right? According to James Surowiecki, the best-selling author of &amp;ldquo;The Wisdom of Crowds&amp;rdquo;, the audience on Millionaire was correct 91% of the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VCSP Cloud Security Presentation</title>
      <link>https://blog.hardcidr.com/security/vcsp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 12:57:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.hardcidr.com/security/vcsp/</guid>
      <description>I gave a presentation to the Virginia Cyber Security Partnership in 2017 regarding Cloud Security! My talk focused on creating a new defense in depth model for public cloud environments, while showing practical examples of how to implement the technology of the new model.
You can see the YouTube video below, which is a recording of that presentation.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vitamin D Supplement Reference</title>
      <link>https://blog.hardcidr.com/supplements/vitamind/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 12:57:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.hardcidr.com/supplements/vitamind/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a big advocate of science-backed supplements to optimize mental and physical performance. These articles represent my own distilled research on effectiveness, risk, and other things to consider before supplementing. To see what supplements I am currently taking, definitely check out the &amp;ldquo;My Current Supplements&amp;rdquo; article at the top of this section. Most of the sources are dervived from Examine.com, which is a great resource, but my intent is to distill it down and add my own research + anecdotes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>